With
with.
.
So. Sabotage wrecking the well
to the back of it who did it.
Like.
This and I know I know I
know you stand you broke
a contract if you broke the norm. It's
like this we look at the stink and it's in
the. Song that.
If I want to sit in the dock I
can do it to do. I think it's
a blinking shame robbing the poor people
like that. Because I'm money back. Then
and like in this microphone is a brother
or a baby you can lean on into C.N.N.
We got to our money thing. I had
ahead of time trying to eat my
a contest with the Hulk My now.
We've given him anything we can
cling to which was developed with.
It was about. The party you would.
Think the government. Paid for.
Did you get I have. Fewer than
twenty minutes ago I came across.
The. Country. Because it's what the few.
Streets in the train the
audience on many many
a terrible row but. We
can't possibly afford it.
The crazy little critters right here always
say we don't cover expenses. That's all
right paid on time going to
the public. Money coming in.
So you say. We're going to be generous
let's do it properly you know that there's
a speech about you know there used to
you. Were right to think you're crazy
and I said God I tell you what you call
an act of God in your face when you don't
get your money back on that.
Plane with a come along and drop
a bomb on you that would be an unfriendly
act within the meaning of the act but if
the Jews rise up of its own accord and
accept Providence as laid down in the act
William the Fourth where an act is defined
as any activity act by actual action you
know one of the blinking lights. You can.
Probably tell you may come that's right
we want our money back and how you're
going to get it apply sanctions are you
familiar with the details of the Covenant
if you studied Article two hundred fifty
seven paragraph twenty four line six says
definitely know. You didn't know that
video you're all ignorant you take my
advice you go off because there's nothing
doing. What do you think you're
doing. And I told you not going to
be delivering a little counterattack there
on the run going to Mike that this is
a gentleman you're going to get your money
back. Don't give in and I will be free.
To ladies and gentlemen I just
think this is it and since you're
all regular patrons and good friends he's
going to let you have your money or no
money back until you go on get oh
please don't pay any attention to
a. Six minute.
Meaning stop responding
a piece of cement. And you. Know
.
I know that feeling I. Thank
you for your trouble I'm
sure you mess with that old I like from.
One. Pocket. How many to see.
How many listening for.
One. Minute. There just going
to be can that be so Mrs
Belloc makes. You laugh now I've got you
ready and in September this could be
because. You know I can
get a subpoena to give me
a digital. If
you don't call this time.
Come on don't be so money.
We didn't have to pay
them back to money after.
All businesswoman Mrs Jones managed to
make the cabbage Brown I'm always telling
you I think. I'll make you
a salad if you then they don't get it I
think head of lettuce no. I don't and we
devastated don't judge it. Never
would have been able to save them
don't even seem very
good when I go. I mean
when he says he to pay them back you
know no it's not that only anything for
a quiet I don't like attention being
thrown around like that. Getting him to
develop forgive me for butting in
a our private affairs but despite
specimen in the beard know what he wanted
a long round square oblong that's
about a selection I just think
a good long lunch you know I did you I
thought you said long ones I found online
I've been eating this if i like they
came home just in time to say that's not
really me I've been in all the afternoon
but I coulda sworn I saw you come in just
about well you were wrong I didn't know
anything about it and to be able committed
that no he resigned down upstairs I had to
call it sorry my mistake I suppose well
here we are.
I thought someone was committing
a murder someone probably is on the screen
that he has I can fix that thank God
George got it doesn't
I just save. I don't.
With.
The not. Like
the others on the most of them.
Myself I look back at it thank you.
And I fight. At times
it is open every locks.
All right in the parts of another.
Those are just as all that happened tonight
except in the yarn I'm not certain but
I could've sworn I saw the look come
back in the middle of it all I do when I
challenged him he didn't know me not
a tall white contempt naturally she would
if she was in it but find some way of
talking to. This complex I want to spit on
this kid something worse than I felt may
happen what's the idea What's the point of
all this with you making trouble at home
to take advantage of what's
going on abroad they meet in
a crowd one hundred one it tell why their
argument is politics or pocket who's
behind it they're the people that you and
I never catch it's the man they imply
that we're.
And you know that but he dangerous
was even stuff like that mind of
a child you only with
a bike and they would be very pleased
with yourself I suppose that would depend
whether with your legal mind content
joined suppose aren't you then I thought
a good for the fate. Of
going to be just. A matter of
think that Plato might think is
a good one and you know Kenya made that
left that makes me think the women like in
so. You're not going back to
make the going out. I'll be
back as soon as I can.
Any spread of profanity. By about Betty.
With. The.
With the move in the book is going
to happen with you that I can't get
here to live on and day with and. With.
That I never can KING Yeah that one of the
things that takes real like that makes
who wrote most think that it
think of. It that that with the.
There's a thing with
a moustache. But it's quite the blackness.
Wasn't that easy to look at and
money to know the need. To sort of
thing to make people buy them I think
you'll agree with them the money
will be didn't mind Men are people
in. The middle London laugh
when one says that with the fear of death
into people it's not helpful to make them
and. They're not comedians in my pocket
I think you can and then there's
a mix. And because I realized what happened
last night was laughable I did write
a lot of this stuff but
you need to their luck
with that page on money when you're
there and I don't for the devil.
I once read
a sign in Piccadilly Circus calling it the
center of the world. And if you give it
appears it in a couple of days and you've
a small parcel in the cloak room of the
underground station what sort of the plans
but we don't know it's
a parcel of course I couldn't
I'm not going to be connected to it and
you think it means lots of black you have
to put somebody else I won't catch it haven't
developed if you think you're so well
off that you know I'm not. You know my
position. Than you will be paid your money
when you use because it's going
to do to some surety that some
kind friends would that's. Not I'm just
going to see this man with
a nice old gentleman
because that's the phone.
Lines I. Don't think it's
a date at the next not miss who do not
want to come to Pro X.
Now if you're not it's no
longer enough want innocence
which is the way out.
This time at least it is
here to contain a high after laying
a million eggs at the man only to
change it to sex I don't blame him.
The.
High I've got it.
Could be the total. Thank. You
Abed corn and the bread
or the why didn't the
a Mrs Belloc. Did years ago
present I don't eat my food
a. You and your crew. Why don't you to
take with me what about if I'm alone what
good which we get I'm not good at something
but I knows I'm in there wants to be
still if it was going to.
Be let's make it simple.
To do what you please. I
don't think you want.
To do standing on it you're fired as
one day you did. Something expensive.
Like it doesn't. Seem.
Right. Setting aside the stakes for a
moment we have here before it can be
a. Try boiling not as
a roast mutton Kentish chicken
putting boil Silverside roast
a line chopped takes kidneys all
roast ducks I think he'd like
a nice steak on toast not
a mix. Poached Egg carrots and but
it's enough to make the roast
beef turn this gravy three
bullocks roasted whole and
a cup of coffee. When you
come up with Americans that
a year ago this wasn't
a good and funny commute to go
to the States but this wasn't
a bit over here I think we're going.
To have next to turning people away.
To make
a one man business. Machine
understand that. As Mr. Know
Like I said I think. This
one happened is opened.
When. I think. And that
means
a lot he says. When he's no
facts he like Usually he I
don't get in the scene with
a long time. So I was I
don't like that that's
a big idea when idea first potential for
a second of going to come down that's
what everyone I'd like to know there's
a mystery about me come to think there's
a mystery about most people haven't you
got some terrible secret Never mind about
what goes on
a tragic death in America because the good
doctor and your husband go on mysterious
Jenny and you don't think. That means
another woman is like what. You look in
you. Trying it might sound
like some level of.
Well like when this is
a she knows nothing is
a nothing at all and make sure things are
set straight answer everything the fact.
That the one second to do it and I know
I'm too tender hearted myself especially
well mannered and whatever I'm not certain
but it is mixed up and this is not
giving away I'm not so sure about that
your assistant what how does it Alexandra
signal by you this morning to follow
this man to the legislative. List is
a faux telephone to call them ten minutes
they're like went to the zoo aquarium
evidently by a point and met a certain
part of an individual who handed him
a paper he then proceeded to
sixty five little code is
a computer version and waiting for him
to come out and report again later isn't
exactly
a mean much to me either. What
I can't understand madam but that's my best
song about it saying all day before you
purchased it perhaps in
a few days it will settle down nothing will
make it settle down I've tried always.
Makes me look silly not
the fault. Isn't it.
I want to Connecticut.
I can make him sing.
Listen to me.
Boy Don't forget watercress and you must
whisper to him may whistle but you're not
made. To guess of course you
want something from my father
Department. Of this way with.
My daughter.
Much better than having street just for
you stricken just to increase it if you.
Keep. To that.
Discipline it.
May be I don't do notice this. My
daughter would like to know too
but there you are it's crafts and she was
there that we all have our crosses to
bear. Everything there
looks pretty good and you
have liked my friend that
if I were to make say
a little tomato sauce with
some straw probably Jack but.
I gather from bad mutual friend that said
it is the day and the hour one brought it
. In for counseling stand to make
a new law you leave it to leave by the time
you receive it everything will be in it
in motion. You seem
a little no good deal they say to yourself
there is one man who didn't the shoe
and. I've been a fighter
always until now but alas I'm
a longer wanted in the front line and I
must keep the fight is supplied but I would
rather be in the other shoe.
My dear just look here.
Yes yes you're right
I must put it there myself.
No harm done. Then I think
everything is quite clear.
Let me hard grandad been there in
all its. Just like this but still.
He might be watching me why not they
probably know too much already there you're
a good one. I will give them
a nice warm welcome if they
do. It didn't feel me.
On Saturday without fail to canaries in
that nice cage or the bit if you don't
forget that it was.
Now stuff I want to annoy.
You take you to. The compound.
Of course I realize you want another
gringos. I'm going to bring both you can
hardly afford lunch at Simpson Canyon is
really quite well off and if they don't
then the business is one of the
big. If you ask me I believe he's
a son of the man. I'm talking. With
and I would say he makes no sound.
Good news event and has taken
a generic. Five day could soon get sick
of it that I wouldn't get to the Seems to
meet. What's needed but I think the world.
That he doesn't need to dignity. So terribly
dignified needs to dignified me day so
I see
a bunch. Of it it'll come to this
and saying it. Is more like two
of us. Taking the Stand I
like it but Ted knows about.
Gangsters and the news missing. He's about
and his gang is not needed so frightened
you'd think some of the quite ordinary
looking like you and me Mr Vernon. Is Right
after we can get into some peace and
soon get off to the most of them in.
Mr Van. Yes. Yes. I'm Gerri
thank.
Goodness today you know. One just think.
That it. May be I want to
bring you any more than I and I.
Well.
Didn't you get a can have
a little bit developed well he doesn't
talk to now speakers that within their
ministry knows. That not.
Where does that lead to that laptop and
the current one you know I'll give Oh not
to be
a surprise Chris it's all come out
of that. Side your head you know I
go. All Down didn't buy
back no good maybe they
are getting I mean our.
Stuff to do that to me
I don't compose I got the main man by me
alone but all that in order to order I'm
only too glad to pay one hundred jobs well
I don't see anything against it I call
in tomorrow about. And
afterwards I'll settle with deal
when you have done the job of
course is the arsenal rules to
burning on Saturday I shan't so
please. I don't follow no no I know
you don't follow us no but they're
a good bet believe me don't forget I
filled in about ten coupons stange
minute about fifteen bombs
so I'm sent out as.
One by no means what are you doing nothing
who hate what is on the cruiser next
door I know NORAD But what happened I
shouldn't get the loudspeaker. The way.
I didn't head in or now and then want to
develop no harm done I hope I'm speaking
back to change the old apple tree.
And I don't and I. That
is the. Soul of Scotland.
Having
a son we're going to do about it but it's
connected to. The last one I'm on life
from not going to do about it saying
this job is all out finished. And keep
scattered and you can tell again tell you
what I know we live. In if you like.
Yesterday it seems that you had
lunch with it in. The mental.
Because you depicted.
Displayed I mean. Anybody
can take you you.
Good to. Speak to mental.
Women clean or day out of them.
With tales gone. Has he gone to
Scotland Yard trying to vent
but I didn't like the idea but I couldn't
refuse his official. That was which along
with this is what it was about don't you
find I know. You must have been changing
funny short films I daresay
you know it should be too.
Busy.
I was trying to get hold of things this
morning but in the end whether the plank No
but it's too late to stop it out it got
out with an order. Alright. Alright.
Alright. With P.V.
I was just phoning about
you. Good. Luck to you.
You're good to me. Yes and. What
made you think of. Someone made the
suggestion. To go and call him Will.
You do any of. This surprise you and
is this going to be.
It was no one on the gimmick about him
like this getting. Nothing showing it is
a. Big. Thing that has no one.
But me but there's nothing practical in all
this. You have this food over trying to
make Stevie and I think you are crazy
you think I enjoy doing my duty I'll be
taking up this job this morning you can
guess why. Not it is that I don't have to
do it you're told who would have given. Me
a life my mother nothing to do with to get
a reliable. Business and this to me would
just get you no idea what that was
it was whatever it was I'm sure my husband
hadn't done anything wrong I hope you're
right. But he's like. We believe that
something going on here connected with
advertisers subject that blackout the other
night to remember. How my husband has
anything to do is Tampa to. Be tell me
that night had been only evening. That
wasn't true I saw him come back
in my own eyes I don't believe.
You're making things very difficult
for me. When I got like you not
a question. About those men that told you
before you the most. You wouldn't do
anything to.
Write.
Feeling.
Guilty. You'll have to wait till
one of them will get to everybody.
Right. By the way. I'm
wondering maybe you could take it
along. There's another little.
No no they will be here when you. Want to
have is added what for but then
they will but. What they do is
this you leave in the cloakroom it
because of the circus. But one.
That's all right you need to take it with
a man. You better get along now.
You'll have to walk all the way. You
know you can take him publicly.
You needn't tell your sister they're
juggling it because you know. All this
thinking you are going to get around
no he. Said no I was terrified.
That's why don't you go. I mean.
You might Bill A Don't forget it's
got to be there when thirty eight.
Do you want to have them taking it to
mean you're over the can't address. The
Strangler that the G.O.P.
Won everything fourteen times better range
parting from it well so long but all of
you can have the crossing back into
darkness not because I was the little bell
again yes I just met.
Kind of when I had to impose on you was
developed I couldn't afford to let you in
on that I put my cards on the
table. I come here to us your
help having not. Seen. Those men
that were here the other night
and I dropped in myself
I've been instructed to get
a little information about them with
a very grateful if you would help. Anyone
else back and give them of course. But
yourself Mr Belin When did you first
come to this country can I get you
a drink was something not many things left
got to think now let's see through but
if you put it down on paper just
a formality. No
.
He said they may have.
Gone to. A hospital next
and I just said when you live there that
I have. This right the engagement. Is
easily attended to how I
am here above all with
a Chilean vet that I have not. Give you
a demonstration that you
put it on the air like
a good one. Because again they need to
give the appearance of the lead up to the
human sex you are now. Gone back. To
the cinema. And then you.
Go on up the spectrum of the mystery.
And.
You guys actually face
consequences. So I'm
stuck not sex. With things.
And. Here I come.
He is.
Blaming.
The it I'll.
Bet the it. Were
the
editor the your.
Children what are they going.
To look at the damage here is one thirty
in the morning meeting on the radio that
they are coming out of there in
a primary vehicle to feel safe in their
flammable one or both big boys but I'm
going to get to get
a good idea that's on the SO MUCH I live.
About the. Let me restring that I wanted
you Bob on your body you can stay as long
you can promise not to set about me or
any of the best news.
You need. A
new.
To me. In new.
Orleans.
Parish.
Listen. To it the Louis.
Blues.
Well everything seems to be all right but
you know if you drink after all are.
We doing
a one two one two now usual phone. Call
but these.
People have been blown up in the.
Two places.
I mean later on.
But on the wrong it's I'm not sure my
own make up your mind but it is anyway.
Well known is something that's filmed in
his lips. But Isabella has been out since
this morning we've had him on you best
go back there and see that one of the
episodes will be so yes yes you better
don't fall into the but if you don't go
inside just keep your eyes open close
confidante that's caught up it.
Is when you think of the river suspense
and. Oh it's all abuse I mean but the films
in it's. No. Being.
Something that you. Think. He's all
right you take it in
south because when you.
Give me a good thing. I did it in
a big. Attic and Isaac.
So. Let's get them on the
right of the senator to have
a Harry break and I don't want to have
a little bit I don't agree that
divided. As I have ever felt it.
Has to do not. Go into Mr very much
and I didn't mean any harm to
come to the book. Is good to
think of tomorrow you'll need all
your wits about you take it on to me
you might sort of peddle will be Reason
number one what would it have
been if you had lost me.
There lying in the Bay Area
to live hearing danger is
a little bit numb us and then you
didn't know quite the right to another
kept to what
a woman it's from that means
you have no business to know.
You left to pull yourself together
my guess but than content and.
You could debate what you want is
a good cry I know how you see if you think
it doesn't touch me good think I
fixed it so that hit big hills.
That I tell you who did your Scotland Yard
friends from next door Ted blame him I
took care of the thing myself but he was
hanging around watching Sky I couldn't get
away.
From. Good can. And that's the future that
I don't know. If we had
to pick up the phone.
Well just to get
a bit. Back
. A bit.
I don't think I want the nick.
Couldn't have been nicked up with.
Do you feel.
You've had it so. Terribly
sorry I don't want to
think. You know I'm here. I have to
escape. You. That's enough I can
of course you don't think I'm
not for his I'd do anything for you you
know that don't you. Think that if.
He's Anything you can do for the things
are not as bad as that you know things is
against him I admit that
he's going to have you.
I know he could give
a the time to tell you. I should and you
told I suppose. Before I'd take him along
I want you to know that.
What have you meant
a lot to me I didn't want to
tell you hype about you but.
You.
Are going to get my code if we're going I
can't stop serving God sake what happened
to you. If you woman have
to go where the police
now call on women.
But.
You can't go through with this kid let
me go. With you you need to. Speed
let me go I know the fact that no
one charge would you stand with
a judge and jury and I'm Kiran. With me.
Idea we're going to get out of all this
Kara. You know no good you can move ahead
with that except tonight we don't need
passports for the coming and if we are so we
can take it's the trainees at nine. Someone
trying in that room to change anyone's
two thousand and eight o'clock in the
morning and a cab and you see me coming
a chance I mean now before anyone can kind
of you said I don't want to get another
word from you I'm going to take that about
being abducted like that is what the
police get teletypes How can you be
to meds adjusted a bird cage with
a bomb I couldn't elsewhere
you could have now had
a head in your coat and my people what
a big risk to to you what about me the
child I mean I lived in one long risk
a month ago I'm getting that text. I get
that but Kate it's been too intimate and
just.
All that tech to. Put this in the on.
The stand was on other
people's i'm sick they support
a man under observation just their
job is making the bitter cinema.
With their politics and
the instructions. You
need to retire is a ribbon
envelope on arrival and
a tape inspector coming from. I just.
Think I'm losing my.
But if it.
Is then.
It is. Not that when.
You mention cali no time now madam I miss
him oh well we will spend the look at
this take me long weekend why See this is
where like no we want to question you can
think only my time I want to make the
statement A What kind of state this is
relative make your take
a later station all right Frank Langella
face into the oven Oh man come to the back
right I'm coming over you wait
till I have been very long in
a minute no but Mrs Belloc Yes not
I'm not a great place to say have
a carpenter how many men
have gone round the back.
Mr BELIN.
Come on them open up. Got
a bomb to clear the cinema
after the old man. Got
a wife already stopped. The audience out.
Of the back gonna come to the news. As
I do I don't know what is happening.
It is not about.
This is not your husband inside. The
failing Spencer. The old man's got
a bum what your husbands
know and you control.
He's.
Gone the only the best place being blown
up and about is all the old insecure and
good it's
a perfectly legal I was pulling for something
you really want to see. And enough to
identify I will be facing you but I got
a prostate my template had. To expect.
Me to look after the husbands
that loan the globe. You
can break it. Up if you inquired
it late the nothing against as
a bonus I guess it's.
The. Way that's clear he said girls and
he said that the look was dead
so you don't need to confide in
a case like this but you said it
before all. You want to tell.
A countryman. The planet
littler.
Than.